<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Minecraft Information</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Minecraft Information</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 18:29:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ilmango - Clay farm</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/clay/1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 21:41:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/clay/1/</guid><description> Clay Java Farms Efficient Renewable Clay Converter | MediaFire | Direct Download |
The mud farm mentioned in the video is this one.
| 22w14a |</description></item><item><title>ilmango | Is Furnace Array Hopper Locking Necessary? | [1.19-]</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/tip-trick/java/lag/1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:16:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/tip-trick/java/lag/1/</guid><description> Lag ilmango - Is Furnace Array Hopper Locking Necessary?</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 1.19 Pre-Release 3</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/1.19pre3/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:49:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/1.19pre3/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 1.19 Pre-Release 3 1.19 Pre-Release 3 We&amp;rsquo;ve now released 1.19 pre-release 3, which will be our last pre-release for this week. In this pre-release we&amp;rsquo;ve tweaked the sonic boom attack and fixed more bugs.
Changes Wardens’ sonic boom attack now bypasses the damage reduction by armor enchantments such as Protection Technical Changes item_interact_start is no longer detectable as a vibration to allow more specific actions be detected, like drink or eat, but item_interact_finish still is Fixed Bugs MC-209932 - Sculk sensors only detect the last turtle egg being broken when being stepped on.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 1.19 Pre-Release 2</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/1.19pre2/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:33:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/1.19pre2/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 1.19 Pre-Release 2 1.19 Pre-Release 2 The second pre-release for 1.19 is now available and it comes with a bunch of bugfixes!
Important to note is that a recent change made it possible for more types of mobs to spawn inside Nether Portals, which caused them to instantly change dimensions after spawning. We will not be making any further changes to this before the release of 1.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 1.19 Pre-Release 1</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/1.19pre1/notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:05:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/1.19pre1/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 1.19 Pre-Release 1 1.19 Pre-Release 1 Presenting the first pre-release of 1.19: The Wild Update!
From now on, you should mostly see bugs being fixed. In addition to that, pre-releases don&amp;rsquo;t follow the regular snapshot cadence of releasing on Wednesdays, so keep an eye out for the next pre-release ;)
As always, a big thank you to the community for your feedback, bugs reported, and awesome ideas throughout the snapshot series.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w17a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w17a/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 18:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w17a/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w17a 22w17a Prepare to drop some sick bleats in the latest Minecraft: Java Edition snapshot! We&amp;rsquo;re bringing in the sweet sounds of the goat horn. There are also some changes to the warden and the allay.
If the technical aspects of chatting is where it&amp;rsquo;s at for you, make sure to check out the changes to chat signing.
Enjoy!
New Features Added Goat Horn!</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w18a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w18a/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 18:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w18a/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w18a 22w18a Another snapshot is now available for Minecraft: Java Edition. This snapshot brings a few gameplay changes and some technical tidbits, such as the place command and cryptographically signed chat commands.
Enjoy!
Changes Allays now follow their liked player even if they can’t see them Allays will only lose track of a player if they are more than 64 blocks away The texture of the sonic boom particle has been updated Vibration listeners such as Sculk Sensors, Sculk Shriekers and Wardens now listen to the closest vibration instead of the first vibration in the tick Technical Changes Banner patterns available in the Loom can now be controlled with tags (banner_pattern/no_item_required for no pattern item and banner_pattern/pattern_item/* for specific banner pattern items) Servers can now define different chat style formats for clients Removed the placefeature command Added the place command The bundled Java runtime has been upgraded to 17.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w19a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w19a/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 18:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w19a/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w19a 22w19a Thursday snapshot! Apart from some bugfixes and some changes to fancy tags and commands, we&amp;rsquo;re introducing &amp;ldquo;chat preview&amp;rdquo; as a way to cryptographically sign chat messages that have been dynamically styled by servers. And for this snapshot only, we&amp;rsquo;ve left in our testing option test-rainbow-chat in server.properties, which can be set to true together with the new previews-chat option for testing. If this is something that interests you, and especially if you run a server, we would love your feedback on it.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w16b/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 20:08:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w16b/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w16b 22w16b Update: We&amp;rsquo;ve now released snapshot 22w16b to fix a crash.
Fixed Bugs MC-250312 - Game crashing when clicking singleplayer || java.lang.NullPointerException: Cannot invoke &amp;#39;java.lang.Comparable.compareTo(Object)&amp;#39; because &amp;#39;pivot&amp;#39; is null. Get the Snapshot Snapshots are available for Minecraft: Java Edition. To install the snapshot, open up the Minecraft Launcher and enable snapshots in the &amp;ldquo;Installations&amp;rdquo; tab.
Snapshots can corrupt your world, so please backup and/or run them in a different folder from your main worlds.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w16a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w16a/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 20:08:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w16a/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w16a 22w16a A chance to re-live the good old times appears in snapshot 22w16a with the ability to de-fragment a Disc – a new Music Disc, to be precise! This snapshot also comes with even more new music, tweaks to the Allay, and to top it all off some random gameplay events are slightly more predictable.
Enjoy!
New Features Added new music Added Disc Fragment 5 and Music Disc 5 Four New Music Tracks The new music tracks are called Ancestry, Aerie, Firebugs, and Labyrinthine They play in certain biomes and in the main menu Music Disc 5 A new music disc has been added to the game.</description></item><item><title>xisumavoid - Warped &amp; Crimson, Fungus &amp; Roots Farm</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/warped_crimson/1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 16:20:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/warped_crimson/1/</guid><description> Warped &amp;amp; Crimson Java Farms Minecraft 1.18 Warped &amp;amp; Crimson, Fungus &amp;amp; Roots Farm | 1.18 |</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w13a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w13a/notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:55:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w13a/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w13a 22w13a Allay, the mob that nobody is really sure how to pronounce, is now entering the latest Minecraft: Java Edition snapshot. Along with our new shiny blue friend, we&amp;rsquo;ve added the ancient cities, which have seen some pretty drastic changes since the experimental snapshot a few weeks ago, so make sure you check them out.
Happy mining!
New Features Added Allay mob Added Ancient Cities Allay Allays will collect all the surrounding items that match the item they are holding Allays will like a player who hands them an item and will bring the items they collect to their liked player If the Allay hears a noteblock play, that noteblock becomes the Allay’s favorite noteblock for 30 seconds.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w14a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w14a/notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:55:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w14a/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w14a 22w14a Mangrove trees! Warm frogs! Mud blocks! More mangrove trees! Today, we’re happy to bring you the most mud-tastic Java snapshot to date!
Sure, it might be our only mud-tastic snapshot to date – but the important thing is that our new biome, mangrove swamp, now is available for testing, along with nitty-gritty features like the recovery compass and other, more technical tidbits.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w15a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w15a/notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:55:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w15a/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w15a 22w15a Let me tell you a little story about hubris. Well, not so much a story as a lament. Because some of you have been thinking that the warden was a little too easy. I won’t name names, but I know you’re out there. Why else would we be adding ranged attacks for this already terrifying mob? Was the sniffing not enough? When will it end?</description></item><item><title>Version Notes | 22w11a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w11a/notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:55:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w11a/notes/</guid><description>Version Notes | 22w11a 22w11a Minecraft: Java Edition is jumping on the Wild Update train! The first snapshot for 1.19 is now available. It contains frogs, the Deep Dark, and a bunch of new blocks. We&amp;rsquo;ve also entered the era of 3D directional audio. Keeping up with the times!
Happy mining!
New Features Added the Deep Dark biome Added Frogs &amp;amp; Tadpoles Added mangrove blocks Added mud and mud brick blocks Added Sculk, Sculk Veins, Sculk Shrieker and Sculk Catalyst blocks Added 3D Directional Audio option Deep Dark Dig into the depths far underground to uncover the darkest biome in Minecraft - the Deep Dark.</description></item><item><title>Version Notes | 22w12a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w12a/notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:55:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w12a/notes/</guid><description>Version Notes | 22w12a 22w12a Waaaaaaaaaaah! It&amp;rsquo;s Wal&amp;hellip; wait that&amp;rsquo;s not it. It&amp;rsquo;s the warden! The spooky, unfriendly (maybe it just wants a hug?) mob is making its way into our latest snapshot.
Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll be seeing some functionality for the sculk shriekers and some fancy new boats (they have chests).
Enjoy!
New Features Added Darkness mob effect Added Sculk Shrieker functionality Added the Warden mob Added boat with chest Added the Swift Sneak enchantment Sculk Shrieker Added functionality to the Sculk Shrieker: Notable for its boney appendages, this block responds to Sculk Sensors detecting vibrations by sending out a warning call to distant Wardens Watch out when stepping on them, as they will feel that too and send out a call!</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes | 22w13</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w13/notes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 14:07:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w13/notes/</guid><description>Patch Notes | 22w13oneBlockAtATime 22w13 Mojang Studios Release New Astonishing Update Saving Minecraft – one block at a time!
Simplicitas.
That, dear reader, is Latin – the language of excessively edgy proverbs and true commitments, like a cringy tattoo inked during mid-teen emo years. Use it lightly and you’ll end up with terms like “Nincompoop” instead of “Cool dude” on your back. And to answer your question: yes, I am working on removing that tattoo, but it takes a while when all you have is soap and water!</description></item><item><title>Pixlriffs | One Block At A Time: The Mini-Series | 22w13</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w13/serie/pixlriffs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 14:07:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/version/java/information/22w13/serie/pixlriffs/</guid><description>Series One Block At A Time: The Mini-Series I Built A Starter House in Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s April Fools Update ▫ Minecraft: One Block At A Time [Ep.1] Farming Infinite Diamonds in Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s April Fools Update ▫ Minecraft: One Block At A Time [Ep.2] A Game-Breaking Storage System in Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s April Fools Update ▫ One Block At A Time [Ep.3] I Insta-Mined Ancient Debris in Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s April Fools Update ▫ One Block At A Time [Ep.</description></item><item><title>Information</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/iron/1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/iron/1/</guid><description> Iron Java Farms Everything To Know About Iron Farming! - Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s Best Farm (#1)</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 1.19 Pre-Release 3</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/1.19pre3/reviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:49:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/1.19pre3/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 1.19 Pre-Release 3 1.19 Pre-Release 3 xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Pre-Release 3 More New Sculk Vibration Events! -- Rays Works Mojang BROKE my Best Farms! 1.19 Pre 2 &amp;amp; 3 Review --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 1.19 Pre-Release 2</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/1.19pre2/reviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:33:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/1.19pre2/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 1.19 Pre-Release 2 1.19 Pre-Release 2 xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Pre-Release 2 - The End Of Portal Farms? -- Rays Works Mojang BROKE my Best Farms! 1.19 Pre 2 &amp;amp; 3 Review -- ilmango Minecraft News: 1.19pre2 Fortress Portal Farms in 1.19 --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 1.19 Pre-Release 1</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/1.19pre1/reviews/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:05:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/1.19pre1/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 1.19 Pre-Release 1 1.19 Pre-Release 1 xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Pre-Release 1 - Mob Spawn Changes &amp;amp; New Vibrations -- wattles WILD UPDATE VERY SOON! Sculk Sensors, Release Dates, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Pre Release 1 -- Rays Works FIRST Pre Release for 1.19 Minecraft! Remove features&amp;hellip; -- ilmango Minecraft News: 1.19pre1 Wither Skeletons No Longer Afraid Of The Dark --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w18a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 19:11:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w18a 22w18a wattles New Place Command, Sonic Boom Update, Instrument Mystery, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w18a -- Rays Works Allay BUFF &amp;amp; Sculk NERF! 1.19 Minecraft News -- ilmango Minecraft News: 22w18a Allay Follows The Player Properly -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W18A Better Allays? Better Attack Beam? --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w19a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w19a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 19:11:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w19a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w19a 22w19a wattles Cancelled Updates, Iron Golem Spawn Change, New Commands + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w19a -- ilmango Minecraft News: 22w19a No Fireflies And Birch Forest This Update -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W19A Birch Forest &amp;amp; Fireflies! Where Are They? --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w17a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:53:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w17a 22w17a Rays Works Warden NEW Loot! + Disc 5 Explained 1.19 Minecraft snapshot review -- wattles Goat Horns, Warden Drop, Sonic Boom Buffs, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w17a -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W17A The Warden Gets A Drop! -- ilmango Minecraft News: 22w17a Sculk XP From Explosions, Goat Horns --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w16a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w16a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:19:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w16a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w16a 22w16a wattles Disc Fragments, New Music, Allay Buffs, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w16a -- Rays Works New Disc OPENS Portal? 1.19 Minecraft snapshot review -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W16A New Record Disc, New Paintings, New Soundtrack! -- ilmango Minecraft News: 22w16b Allay Buffed, New Music Disc --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w15a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w15a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 19:03:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w15a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w15a 22w15a ilmango Minecraft News: 22w15a Care Bear Attack For The Warden / Note Block Change Reverted -- Rays Works Warden Sonic ATTACK! 1.19 Minecraft snapshot review -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W15A SONIC BOOM! The Warden&amp;rsquo;s Ranged Attack -- wattles Warden Sonic Boom, HUGE Mangrove Swamp Improvements, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w15a --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w13</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w13/reviews/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 23:17:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w13/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w13 22w13 Rays Works Minecraft April Fools- ASTONISHING UPDATE! We BROKE Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s April Fools! wattles MINECRAFT ONE BLOCK AT A TIME UPDATE! | Minecraft Snapshot 22w13oneblockatatime xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W13oneblockatatime - Inventory Fixed Forever! Pixlriffs Minecraft April Fools Snapshot Reaction! ▫ One Block At A Time w/ Ulraf, Cubfan135 &amp;amp; BrunoDanUy</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w11a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w11a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 20:01:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w11a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w11a 22w11a xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W11A Frogs, Tadpoles, Froglights &amp;amp; More! -- Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W11A - Part 2 - The Copper Horn&amp;rsquo;s Secret --</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w12a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w12a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 20:01:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w12a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w12a 22w12a xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W12A Derpy Wardens &amp;amp; Waterlogged Leaves! ilmango Minecraft News: 22w12a Chest Boats Are Game Changers wattles WARDEN, SWIFT SNEAK ENCHANT CHANGES, + MORE! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w12a</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w13a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w13a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 20:01:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w13a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w13a 22w13a xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W13A New Ancient City &amp;amp; The Redstone Secrets Below&amp;hellip; wattles Ancient City Overhaul with Redstone Secrets + Loot, Allay, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w13a Rays Works Secret Redstone Rooms in Ancient City! 1.19 Minecraft Snapshot ilmango Minecraft News: 22w13a Allays And 2011 Redstone</description></item><item><title>Reviews | 22w14a</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w14a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 20:01:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w14a/reviews/</guid><description>Reviews | 22w14a 22w14a wattles Mangrove Swamp, Respawn Compass, Echo Shards, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w14a -- ilmango Minecraft News: 22w14a Renewable Clay, Challenging Mangrove Trees And Recovery Compass -- Rays Works Echo Shard? 1.19 Minecraft + Recovery Compass, Mangrove Biome! -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W14A Mangrove Swamp &amp;amp; Recovery Compass</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 19:56:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/about/</guid><description>Home GitHub &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; PyPi &amp;nbsp; Made by Ran#.
Contact ran-n@tutanota.com ran-n@tutanota.com const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.getElementById(elementId).innerHTML; temp.setAttribute("value", text); document.body.appendChild(temp); temp.select(); document.execCommand("copy"); document.body.removeChild(temp); }; For business inquiries use this email: ran-n@tutanota.com
Donations &amp;nbsp; 88Rezd6ZQzaCb1s7K1tRCiCaDzuHrfYsn4q348jJuePpLs84JNsWEghMAZZgzpDPrqD4PBxk7hwMkSdNQ4CLqFHyPVLdX1D const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.</description></item><item><title>2022</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/minecrafter/2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 22:45:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/minecrafter/2022/</guid><description>Minecrafter 2022 jfnhlasd</description></item><item><title>tangotek - Iron Titan</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/iron/1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 21:11:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/iron/1/</guid><description>Iron Java Farms The Iron Titan - Minecraft Iron Golem Farm - 2600 Iron/hr (Works in 1.13) | MediaFire | Direct Download |
-=-=-=&amp;ndash;==-=- CORRECTION =-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-
(At 33:58 into the video)
If your center door line has a positive X coordinate, then always place doors on the EAST side first, THEN WEST. (East-to-West &amp;hellip; East-to-West&amp;hellip;)
If your center door line has a negative X coordinate, then always place doors west then east as in the video.</description></item><item><title>GruvaGuy - Tileable Automatic Potion Brewer</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/redstone/bedrock/auto-brewer/1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:02:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/redstone/bedrock/auto-brewer/1/</guid><description> Auto-Brewers Minecraft Tileable Potion Brewer, All the Potions on Demand! Minecraft Bedrock 1.18 | 1.18 |</description></item><item><title>ilmango - Mud farm</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/mud/1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 18:29:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/farm/java/mud/1/</guid><description> Mud Java Farms Much Better Auto Mud Farm | MediaFire | Direct Download |
| 22w11a | 1.18.2 |</description></item><item><title>Breogann</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/breogann/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/breogann/</guid><description>Creators Galego English Castellano Breogann Creador de contido especializado en gameplays.
Youtube English &amp;nbsp; Galego &amp;nbsp; Castellano &amp;nbsp; By mention order, the channels in english, galician and spanish.
Odysee English &amp;nbsp; Galego &amp;nbsp; Castellano &amp;nbsp; By mention order, the channels in english, galician and spanish.</description></item><item><title>docm77</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/docm77/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/docm77/</guid><description>Creators English docm77 YouTube &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Twitch &amp;nbsp; Patreon &amp;nbsp; docm77@nevaly.com Correo const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.getElementById(elementId).innerHTML; temp.setAttribute("value", text); document.body.appendChild(temp); temp.select(); document.execCommand("copy"); document.body.removeChild(temp); }; German content creator that uploads only on english.
Especialized in let&amp;rsquo;s plays, redstone and technical minecraft.</description></item><item><title>EthosLab</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/ethoslab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/ethoslab/</guid><description>Creators English EthosLab Youtube &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Canadian content creator that only uploads on english.
Specialized in farming, redstone, gampleays/let&amp;rsquo;s plays and technical minecraft.</description></item><item><title>FalseSymmetry</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/false-symmetry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/false-symmetry/</guid><description>Creators English FalseSymmetry Main Youtube Channel &amp;nbsp; Livestream Youtube Channel &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Twitch &amp;nbsp; Instagram &amp;nbsp; Patreon &amp;nbsp; falsesymmetry@outlook.com@outlook.com Email const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.getElementById(elementId).innerHTML; temp.setAttribute("value", text); document.body.appendChild(temp); temp.select(); document.execCommand("copy"); document.body.removeChild(temp); }; Descriptions English content creator that only uploads in english.</description></item><item><title>Grian</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/grain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/grain/</guid><description>Creators English Grian Youtube &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Instagram &amp;nbsp; Facebook &amp;nbsp; GrianBusiness@gmail.com Gmail const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.getElementById(elementId).innerHTML; temp.setAttribute("value", text); document.body.appendChild(temp); temp.select(); document.execCommand("copy"); document.body.removeChild(temp); }; Descriptions English content creator that only uploads in english and is specialized in building.
Youtube Youtube &amp;nbsp; This channel focuses on gaming (specifically minecraft) content aimed at a general audience.</description></item><item><title>Gruva Guy</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/gruva-guy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/gruva-guy/</guid><description>Creators English Gruva Guy YouTube &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Twitch &amp;nbsp; Discord &amp;nbsp; Patreon &amp;nbsp; gruvaguy@gmail.com Gmail const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.getElementById(elementId).innerHTML; temp.setAttribute("value", text); document.body.appendChild(temp); temp.select(); document.execCommand("copy"); document.body.removeChild(temp); }; English content creator that only uploads in english.
Specialized in farming and technical bedrock minecraft.</description></item><item><title>ilmango</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/ilmango/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/ilmango/</guid><description> Creators English ilmango Youtube &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Twitch &amp;nbsp; scicraftilmango@gmail.com Correo const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.getElementById(elementId).innerHTML; temp.setAttribute("value", text); document.body.appendChild(temp); temp.select(); document.execCommand("copy"); document.body.removeChild(temp); }; German content creator that only uploads in english.
Specialized in farms and technical minecraft.
Contact scicraftilmango@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>impulseSV</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/impulsesv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/impulsesv/</guid><description>Creators English impulseSV web &amp;nbsp; Main Youtube Channel &amp;nbsp; Secondary Youtube Channel &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Twitch &amp;nbsp; Patreon &amp;nbsp; Instagram &amp;nbsp; Facebook &amp;nbsp; TikTok &amp;nbsp; impulsesv@pbnj.gg Main YT Channel Email const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.</description></item><item><title>Mob-Switch | LogicalGeekBoy | [1.18]</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/exploit/java/mob-switch/1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/technical-minecraft/exploit/java/mob-switch/1/</guid><description>How To Stop Mobs Spawning - Easy Mob Switch Tutorial | Simply Minecraft (Java Edition 1.18) Mob Switchs</description></item><item><title>Pixlriffs</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/pixlriffs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/pixlriffs/</guid><description> Creators English Pixlriffs Youtube &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Instagram &amp;nbsp; English content creator that only uploads in english.
Contact business@pixlriffs.com</description></item><item><title>Rays Works</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/rays-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/rays-works/</guid><description>Creators English Rays Works Youtube &amp;nbsp; Twitch &amp;nbsp; Reddit &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Discord &amp;nbsp; Patreon &amp;nbsp; Paypal &amp;nbsp; Content creator from the USA that uploads content only in english.
Specialized in farms and technical minecraft.
Schedule On twitch Sun, Wed, Fri, Sat at ~2pm EST and streams are archived there if you miss the live stream.</description></item><item><title>Tango Tek</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/tango-tek/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/community/creator/tango-tek/</guid><description>Creators English Tango Tek YouTube &amp;nbsp; Twitter &amp;nbsp; Twitch &amp;nbsp; Patreon &amp;nbsp; Paypal &amp;nbsp; tangotek1@gmail.com Gmail const copyToClipboard = (elementId) = { const temp = document.createElement("input"); const text = document.getElementById(elementId).innerHTML; temp.setAttribute("value", text); document.body.appendChild(temp); temp.select(); document.execCommand("copy"); document.body.removeChild(temp); }; Content creator from the USA that uploads content only in english.
Specialized in farms and technical minecraft.</description></item></channel></rss>