<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>22w17a on Minecraft Information</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/</link><description>Recent content in 22w17a on Minecraft Information</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:50:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Patch Notes</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 18:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/notes/</guid><description>22w17a Prepare to drop some sick bleats in the latest Minecraft: Java Edition snapshot! We&amp;rsquo;re bringing in the sweet sounds of the goat horn. There are also some changes to the warden and the allay.
If the technical aspects of chatting is where it&amp;rsquo;s at for you, make sure to check out the changes to chat signing.
Enjoy!
New Features Added Goat Horn! Goat Horn A Goat Horn drops when a Goat rams a tree or any other hard block that occurs naturally where Goats spawn (Logs, Stone, Packed Ice, Iron Ore, Copper Ore, or Emerald Ore) Other solid blocks are unfamiliar to the Goat, so it won’t ram them Use the horn to play a loud sound that can be heard from afar Each horn has its own sound based on the Goat it originated from There are 8 Goat Horn variants, 4 of them exclusive to screaming Goats Goat Horns can sometimes be found in Pillager Outposts Changes The Allay connecting with Note Blocks is now better visualized by the vibration particle The Allay connecting with Note Blocks can now be blocked by Wool Blocks again Replaced realms subtle selected world highlight with a clear green checkmark Updated the Brewing Stand’s base UVs and texture to match a graphical fix in Bedrock Edition Explosions caused by player-ignited TNT now cause experience to drop from broken blocks (such as ore blocks and sculk) We will be keeping an eye on feedback for this change, it might change in a future update Sculk blocks now have very low blast resistance Warden balancing Warden Their ranged attack will now: Bypass shields and armor Deal 10 damage instead of 30 damage, and the cooldown has been reduced from 5 seconds to 2 seconds Display a custom death message Wardens now drop a single Sculk Catalyst upon death Technical Changes Signed Chat Removed dampenable_vibrations game event tag Multiplayer Secure Chat Signing This is the first step in a process to provide more security and player safety features for in-game chat.</description></item><item><title>Reviews</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:53:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w17a/reviews/</guid><description>Rays Works Warden NEW Loot! + Disc 5 Explained 1.19 Minecraft snapshot review -- wattles Goat Horns, Warden Drop, Sonic Boom Buffs, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w17a -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W17A The Warden Gets A Drop! -- ilmango Minecraft News: 22w17a Sculk XP From Explosions, Goat Horns --</description></item></channel></rss>