<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>22w18a on Minecraft Information</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/</link><description>Recent content in 22w18a on Minecraft Information</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 18:52:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Patch Notes</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 18:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/notes/</guid><description>22w18a Another snapshot is now available for Minecraft: Java Edition. This snapshot brings a few gameplay changes and some technical tidbits, such as the place command and cryptographically signed chat commands.
Enjoy!
Changes Allays now follow their liked player even if they can’t see them Allays will only lose track of a player if they are more than 64 blocks away The texture of the sonic boom particle has been updated Vibration listeners such as Sculk Sensors, Sculk Shriekers and Wardens now listen to the closest vibration instead of the first vibration in the tick Technical Changes Banner patterns available in the Loom can now be controlled with tags (banner_pattern/no_item_required for no pattern item and banner_pattern/pattern_item/* for specific banner pattern items) Servers can now define different chat style formats for clients Removed the placefeature command Added the place command The bundled Java runtime has been upgraded to 17.</description></item><item><title>Reviews</title><link>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/reviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 19:11:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ran-n.github.io/minecraft_info/en/minecraft/versions/java/information/22w18a/reviews/</guid><description>wattles New Place Command, Sonic Boom Update, Instrument Mystery, + More! | Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22w18a -- Rays Works Allay BUFF &amp;amp; Sculk NERF! 1.19 Minecraft News -- ilmango Minecraft News: 22w18a Allay Follows The Player Properly -- xisumavoid Minecraft 1.19 Snapshot 22W18A Better Allays? Better Attack Beam? --</description></item></channel></rss>